Same surf. New turf.
Teen Beach 2 is a tv movie, family, comedy film directed by Jeffrey Hornaday.
When characters from the movie musical “Wet Side Story” get stuck in the real
world, teens Brady and Mack must find a way to return them home.
Brady, played by Ross Lynch.
McKenzie 'Mack' Fox, played by Maia Mitchell.
Lela, played by Gracie Gillam.
Tanner, played by Garrett Clayton.
Butchy, played by John DeLuca.
Cheechee, played by Chrissie Fit.
Teen Beach 2 is a 2015 American musical teen comedy drama film
released as a Disney Channel Original Movie.
The sequel to the 2013 film Teen Beach Movie, it was again directed by Jeffrey Hornaday, from a screenplay by
the writing team of Matt and Bill Eddy, and a story conceived by Robert Horn and Dan Berendsen.
Ross Lynch, Maia Mitchell, Grace Phipps, Garrett Clayton, John DeLuca, Chrissie Fit, Jordan Fisher, Kent Boyd, Mollee Gray, William Loftis, and
Jessica Lee Keller reprise their roles from the first film, joined by newcomers Piper Curda, Ross Butler, Raymond Cham Jr., and Beth Lacke.
Teen Beach 2 premiered on Disney Channel on June 26, 2015.
The film was the first sequel of a Disney Channel Original Movie in five
years, the previous one being Camp Rock 2: The Final Jam (2010).
The film explores themes of high school, teen movie, teenager.
The tone is lighthearted.